laptopninja.io 2017-03-09

# Privacy Policy - LaptopNinja

**Last Updated: July 21, 2013** |  Published: July 21, 2013 by 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you use or register on our site.

When using our site, ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## Cookies

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

We work with the following affiliate advertisers using cookies in order to track outgoing links as part of performance marketing campaigns.

  * Amazon.com – Visit the Amazon [Advertising Preferences](http://www.amazon.com/gp/dra/info) to Opt-out of certain advertising cookies
  * CommissionJunction – Click [Here](http://www.conversantmedia.co.uk/opt-out) to Install Conversant Opt-out Cookie
  * LinkShare
  * BHPhotoVideo

You may opt-out of receiving cookies by adjusting your web browser settings to reject cookies for any / all advertisers.

## What is a cookie?

“Cookies” are files that are stored on your web-enabled client (such as your web browser or mobile device) and are used to improve your experience when seeing web and mobile advertisements and ensure that when you click on an ad, you are sent to the correct click-through destination. Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies (see below). However, if you choose not to accept cookies, you may not be able to use all services on websites and you may see more alternative advertising, as we will not be able to limit what you see using cookies. There are many misconceptions about cookies. Cookies cannot erase your hard drive, install programs, or collect PII from your browser or device. Thus, Conversant does not use Cookies or web beacons to retrieve PII from your computer. Cookies are passive and simply used for transferring anonymous information about your online consumer behavior.

## Why do we use cookies?

Cookies allow the server to recognise you when you revisit a website. Websites are able to read and write these files, allowing them to store things like personalization details or user preferences. They are widely used in order to make websites work properly and more efficiently, as well as to provide business and marketing information to the owners of the site. We may use cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as frequency of display. Cookies are also used for statistical purposes. They track how many individual unique users we have on our website, how often they visit our website, and determine the effectiveness of online advertisements. There is further information please visit the European Digital Advertising Alliance if you click here: www.edaa.eu. We will use the data that we collect through our use of these cookies to ensure that you see relevant and useful advertisements when you visit our website and/or use our services.

## Our Cookies Policy

**Here is a list of all the cookies that are set and  their purpose:**

**Session Cookies**  are used only during your visit to the Sites and are erased once you close your browser;

**Persistent Cookies**  remain on your browser for a period of time, usually for several years from your last visit to the Sites, and enable us to remember you on subsequent visits to provide more relevant content to you on such Sites.

**Anonymous** **A** **nalytics** **C** **ookies:  **every time a user visits our website, web analytics software provided by a third party generates an anonymous analytics cookie. This cookie can tell us whether or not the site you are viewing has been visited before. It allows us to track such things as how many individual users we have and which browsers users are utilising.

**Member** **A** **rea/Registration** **C** **ookies:  **when you register with us, we generate cookies that represent whether you are signed in or not. Our servers use these cookies to note which account you are signed in with, and where applicable, if you are allowed access to a particular service.

**Advertising** **C** **ookies** **:** are used to determine whether you have seen an advertisement or type of advertisement and how long it has been since you saw that advertisement. In order to do this, we place a cookie on your machine when advertising is shown. We may use cookies to more accurately target advertising to you. These cookies are anonymous. We also set anonymous cookies to users on certain third party sites. If you receive one of those cookies, we may then use it to identify you as having visited that site if you later visit another site. Based on this information, we may serve targeted advertising.

Our cookies do not store sensitive information such as your name and address. If you would rather restrict, block or delete cookies, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this.

## Managing Your Cookies

**Changing your cookie settings**

To enable or disable cookies, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the ‘Help’, ‘Tools’ or ‘Edit’ facility). Alternatively, see below for specific information about how to enable or disable cookies.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://laptopninja.io/terms-and-conditions/>

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us here or using the information below.

US: +1 4159354031  
ZA: + 27 846767555  
Skype: vikingcorp.cc

Postal Address:

33 Fitzroy Street  
Grahamstown  
Eastern Cape  
South Africa  
6139
